kidsloverscenter.com 2017-06-23

# Privacy Policy - WeetNow

[Home](http://www.weetnow.net/) Privacy Policy

The owners of www.weetnow.com follow a very strict privacy policy. Being an established news and media website, we cater to the needs of the users and do not meddle with their privacy in any form whatsoever.

  1. We value the trust you have in us by giving us your personal information. We will always use your personal information in a manner that is justified and worthy of that trust.
  2. We will provide clear information about how we use your personal information. We shall maintain transparency with you about the information we collect, what we do with it, with whom we share it and who you should contact lest you have any concerns.
  3. We will take all steps to protect your information from misuse and keep it secure.
  4. No information provided by you, will be shared or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

Here are some of the basic segments of our privacy policy: ** **

**What type of information do we collect?**

We do not collect any kind of information from your end for just browsing through our website. However, we do gather some basic information from you in case you choose to register with us, or fill out a form. The type of information we might collect from you are:

  * Name
  * Age
  * Email address
  * Gender
  * Nationality

**Why do we need your information?**

All or some of the basic information provided by you may be used in one of the following ways by us:

  * To personalise your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To build and maintain a healthy customer relationship
  * To cater to the special needs of our users
  * To manage the operations of this site
  * To meet legal requirements, if any

**How do we protect your information?**

The database of our website is accessible only to those authorised with us and they guarantee to keep your private information confidential. By doing this, we intend to create a high level of trust with our users.

**What about third party links used in our website?    **

You should keep in mind that when you visit any third party website from our website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Hence, we take no responsibility or liability for the content or information provided by such third party websites.

**Will there be any changes to this Privacy Policy?**

weetnow reserves the right to change this privacy policy from time to time with or without notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here itself.

**NOTE:**   We suggest you go through our privacy policies on a regular basis to ensure you understand our current policies.

In case you have any query or question regarding our privacy policy, you may contact us at weetnowofficial@gmail.com
